Guide to the Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers AIA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers
1916-2010, undated
1940-1997
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Cudahy, Dorothy Hayden, 1922-2010
AIA.001
53.9 Linear Feet 6 record cartons, 6 oversized flat boxes, 6 custom boxes, 4 CD boxes, 27 LP boxes, 32 vinyl boxes, 6 manuscript boxes, 4 oversized folders, and 1 media box
95 Megabytes in 39 graphics
Dorothy Hayden Cudahy (1922-2010) was an Irish-American woman active in Irish-American social organizations in New York City and host of the Irish Memories radio program from 1943 to 1990. She married John Cudahy (1920-1994) in 1947 and they had one son, Sean (1950-1997). Dorothy was one of the first female parking enforcement officers for the New York City Department of Traffic and retired as the Chief of Administration of the Bureau of Enforcement of the NYC Transportation Department in 1982. She was the first woman elected president of the Kilkenny Association in 1984 and the first woman Grand Marshall of the New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade in 1989. The Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers document the life and work of Dorothy Hayden Cudahy, dating from 1918 to 2010, with the bulk of material dating between the 1940s and the 1990s. Materials include audio recordings, correspondence, print and born-digital photographs, financial documents, writings and speeches, ephemera, clothing, and newspaper clippings. These materials document Dorothy and John's professional and social accomplishments, in particular Dorothy's campaigns for and election as the first female St. Patrick's Day Parade Grand Marshall in 1989, and Dorothy's over 50 years as host of the Irish Memories radio program.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Dorothy Hayden Cudahy, 1996; an additional accretion was donated in 2012. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 1997.019 and 2012.027.
Arrangement
Collection is organized into six series, one of which has been arranged in two sub-series. Material in each series is arranged alphabetically with the exception of materials in Series V, which have not been arranged by an archivist. The series are as follows:
Series I. Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Files, 1936-2010
Sub-series I.A. Personal Material, 1936-2010
Sub-series I. B. Irish Memories Material, 1943-2000
Series II. John J. Cudahy Files, 1925-1994
Series III. Photographs, 1918-2009
Series IV. Ephemera, 1937-2006
Series V. Commercial Recordings, 1916-1992
Series VI. Irish Memories Radio Program Recordings, 1944-1997
Biographical Note
Dorothy Hayden Cudahy (1922-2010) was an Irish-American woman active in Irish-American social organizations in New York City and host of Irish Memories radio program from 1943 to 1990. She married John Cudahy (1920-1994) in 1947 and had one son, Sean (1950-1997). Dorothy was a graduate of the New York Institute of Technology, and worked as one of the first female parking enforcement officers for the New York City Department of Traffic and retired as the Chief of Administration of the Bureau of Enforcement of the NYC Transportation Department in 1982. She was the first woman elected president of the Kilkenny Association in 1984, the first woman Grand Marshall of the New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade in 1989, and a founding member of the Irish Institute of New York.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
American Irish Citizens Committee for the Re-election of William O'Dwyer AIA 002
Mick Moloney Irish American Music and Popular Culture Collection, Part I: Commercial Recordings AIA 031.1
Scope and Contents
The Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers document the life and work of Dorothy Hayden Cudahy, dating from 1918 to 2010, with the bulk of material dating between the 1940s and the 1990s. Materials include audio recordings, correspondence, print and born-digital photographs, writings and speeches, ephemera, clothing, and newspaper clippings. These materials document Dorothy's professional and social accomplishments, in particular Dorothy's campaigns for and election as the first female St. Patrick's Day Parade Grand Marshall in 1989, her participation in Irish-American social organizations in New York City, and Dorothy's over 40 years as host of the Irish Memories radio program. The audio recordings consist of approximately 2000 commercial audio recordings of Irish and Irish-American music, and recordings of Irish Memories from James Hayden's tenure as host as well as Dorothy's tenure. The commercial audio recordings consist of 33 rpm, 45 rpm, 78 rpm grooved discs; printed inventories are available for the 33 rpm and 78 rpm recordings. The recordings of the radio program consist of Fidelipac recordings, audiocassettes, and CDs, all of which have been transferred to access copies. Other material documenting the weekly Irish Memories radio program includes playlists, administrative documents, and notes for interviews. The correspondence consists of letters written to Dorothy regarding her candidacy for Grand Marshal of the New York City St. Patrick's Day parade in the 1980s, letters written by family and friends to Dorothy and John regarding personal topics, correspondence between John and others during his military service in World War II, and correspondence regarding the Irish Memories stage revue. The newspaper clippings document Dorothy's election as the first female Grand Marshal of the New York City St. Patrick's Day parade in 1989, the Irish Memories stage revue and radio program, and John Cudahy's and James Hayden's articles written for Irish-American newspapers.
The print photographs document Dorothy's participation in social and political events in New York City, including meeting city government officials, being honored by the New York City and State governments, multiple New York City and other cities's St. Patrick's Day parades, Irish-American social organization events, and informal gatherings of family and friends. There are photographs of Irish and Irish-American musicians collected by James Hayden and photographs of Dorothy Hayden's Irish Steppers. There are five photograph collages, possibly created for Dorothy's wake or funeral, depicting mainly social events with some photographs from her early life and Dorothy with her husband, son, and her son's family. The born-digital photographs consist of images of plaques commemorating the work and accomplishments of Dorothy and John. Ephemera in the collection consists of plaques, booklets, postcards, holiday cards, sashes, a football, and event decorations. The plaques commemorate the work and accomplishments of Dorothy and John. The booklets document annual meetings and dinners for the Ancient Order of the Hibernians and the County Clare Patriotic and Benevolent Society Association. The sashes read "Free Joe Doherty" and were worn at St. Patrick's Day parades by Dorothy and others to bring attention to the case of Joe Doherty, a member of the Provisional Irish Republican Army who fought against extradition to Northern Ireland after being arrested and held in jail in New York City in the 1980s and 1990s. The bulk of the writings and speeches consist of handwritten speeches given by Dorothy at various political and social events, in particular St. Patrick's Day parades and at Ancient Order of Hibernians committee meetings for planning the parades. Other writings include drafts of newspaper articles written by John in the 1940s regarding soccer matches. The clothing consists of the dress, coat, hat, and boots that Dorothy wore as Grand Marshal at the 1989 New York City St. Patrick's Day parade.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Some audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Tamiment Library & Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information. Access CDs for some audiovisual materials in the collection are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Separated Materials
Records separated from the Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers are included in the Gaelic Athletic Association Collection, AIA 028.
Compact discs.; Broadcasts.; Postcards.; Audiocassettes.; Long-playing records.; Correspondence.; Greeting cards.; Irish Americans -- Music.; Irish Americans -- Social life and customs.; Parades -- New York (State) -- New York.; Saint Patrick's Day -- New York (State) -- New York; Women -- New York (State) -- New York -- Societies and clubs; Photographs.; Radio programs -- United States.; Cudahy, John J., 1920-1994
- Series I. Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Files, 1936-2010; 4.7 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 flat box
  Scope and Contents
  Materials in this series consists of newspaper clippings, correspondence, memoranda, material objects, and financial records documenting Dorothy Hayden Cudahy's personal and professional lives, including her career in the New York City Department of Traffic, the Irish Memories radio program, her step dance troupe, and her involvement with various Irish and Irish-American organizations. Materials in this series date from 1936 to 2010. Of note are music playlists for the radio show and materials concerning Dorothy Cudahy's campaign to become the Grand Marshal of the New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade.
  - Sub-series I.A. Personal Material, 1936-2010; 2.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 flat box
    This sub-series consists of materials documenting Dorothy Hayden Cudahy's personal and family lives, her work in the New York City Department of Traffic, and her campaigns to become the first female Grand Marshal of the New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade. Material in this sub-series dates from 1936 to 2010, and includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, memoranda, and material objects.
    - Awards, 1982-1989 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Calendar, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Certificates, 1985-1989 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1990; Undated (Box 47, Folder 20-21)
    - Ancient Order of Hibernians St. Patrick's Day Parade Committee (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Department of Traffic, New York City, 1960, 1979, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1, Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Doherty, Joe, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Education, 1940; 1977 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Hayden, James A. (Father), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Interview with John [Cudahy?] on Relationship with Cardinal Terence Cooke, Undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Ireland's 32 (Song) Copyright, Apr 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ireland Trips, 1977-1993 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Irish House Parties, Undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Irish Institute Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Mid-Hudson St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1965-2010 (Box 47, Folder 5-6, 18, 24-25)
    - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade--Correspondence, 1985-1995 (Box 47, Folder 7, Box 48, Folder 1)
    - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade--Nomination, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1960s, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1960s (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1957-1987 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Palm Beach St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Parade Grand Marshall Campaign [Saint Patrick's Day Parade], 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Parade Grand Marshall Mailing Lists [Saint Patrick's Day Parade], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Parade Grand Marshall Newspaper Clippings [Saint Patrick's Day Parade], 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1944-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Personal Memorabilia, 1936-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Speeches, Undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Sponsorship of James Kilroy's Immigration to the U.S., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Wedding, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series I. B. Irish Memories Material, 1943-2000; 4.5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 2 manuscript boxes
    This sub-series consists of materials documenting Dorothy Hayden Cudahy's work as an entertainer, mainly as the host of Irish Memories from 1943 to 1990. Material in this sub-series dates from 1943 to 2000 and includes contracts, playlists, ephemera, sponsor lists, and financial material regarding financial sponsors for the show.
    - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), 1973-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists--Membership Cards, 1982-1988 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Broadcast Agreements and Regulations, 1962-1963, 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1990, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Dorothy Hayden Cudahy's Irish Steppers, 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 14, Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Erin-USA Irish-American Revue, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Irish Memories Radio Program, Undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Irish Memories--notes, Undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Irish Memories Stage Revue: Correspondence and Contracts, 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Irish Memories Stage Revue: Programs, notices, Flyers, 1943-1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Irish Memories Stage Review, 1951, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Letterhead (Radio Station WEVD/Irish Memories), undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda, 1952, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Music Playlists, 1965-1966, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Music Playlists, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Music Playlists, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Music Playlists, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Music Playlists, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Music Playlists, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Music Playlists, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Music Playlists, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Music Playlists, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Music Playlists, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1966, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Notes on Music Collection and Album Covers (Photocopies), undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Program Reports (WNWK), Apr 1990-Nov 1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Program Report Logs (WNWK, empty), undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Radio Show Notes, 1979-1980, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Scripts and Interviews, 1980-1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Sponsor Ad Scripts and Instructions, 1968, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Sponsor Invoices: A-Budweiser, 1959-1970, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sponsor Invoices: Budweiser Beer, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Sponsor Invoices: C-I, 1966-1970, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Sponsor Invoices: J-R, 1966-1970, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Sponsor Invoices: S-W, 1965-1970, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Sponsor Rate Card and Money Order Receipts, 1958-1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Sponsor Lists, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Weekly Sponsor Lists, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Weekly Sponsor Lists, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Weekly Sponsor Lists, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Weekly Sponsor Lists, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Weekly Sponsor Lists, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Weekly Sponsor Lists, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Weekly Sponsor Lists, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Weekly Sponsor Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, Jan 1973-Jun 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, Jul 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, Jan 1974-Jun 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, Jul 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - WEVD Sponsor Invoices, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Series II. John J. Cudahy Files, 1925-1994; 2.8 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  Biographical Note
  John J. Cudahy (1920-1994) was an Irish-American interested in Irish culture and social organizations. He married Dorothy Hayden Cudahy in 1947, and had one son, Sean. John was a president of the Clare Association of New York, member of the Ancient Order of Hibernians and the Kilkenny Association, and was a delegate to the United Irish Counties. He served as a delegate to the St. Patrick's Day Parade Committee from the Clare Association.
  This series consists of correspondence, financial records, newspaper editorials, and photographs concerning the life and interests of John J. Cudahy. Topics include Gaelic games matches, Cudahy's service in the United States Army during World War II, and his involvement in Irish and Irish American organizations. Material in this series dates from 1925 to 1994.
  - Colrox Baseball Club, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Cathedral College and Cathedral Prep, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1943-Oct 1943 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1943-1945, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Coronation Announcements, 1937-1947 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Personal, 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Postcards, 1933-1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: St. Joseph's Seminary, 1940-1944 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: St. Joseph's Seminary Christmas Cards, 1943, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: WWII Personnel, 1936-1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: WWII Personnel, Jan 1943-Aug 1943 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: WWII Personnel, Sep 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: WWII Personnel, 1944-1945, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - County Clare P. B. & S. Association, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Eulogy and Obituaries, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Expenses: Other, circa 1944, circa 1954, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Gaelic Games Match Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gaelic Games Match Reports, 1944-1946 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Irish Echo: Voice of the Youthful Gaels, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Membership; Professional/Social Organizations, 1940-1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Retirement, Undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Rose Cottage: Condemnation and Move Out, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Rose Cottage: Furniture, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Rose Cottage: Hardware and Repairs, 1951-1953, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Rose Cottage: Mortgage and Insurance Records, 1925-1960 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Rose Cottage: Permits and Violations, circa 1939-1958 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Rose Cottage: Photographs, Nov 1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Rose Cottage: Real Estate Taxes, 1946-1964 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Rose Cottage: Rent Records, circa 1948-1953 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Rose Cottage: Utility Bills and Taxes, 1940-1960 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Trip to Ireland: Cruise Ship Ephemera, Jul 1933-Sep 1933 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Trip to Ireland: Correspondence, Travel Guides, and Souvenirs, Jul 1933-Sep 1933, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Army Service, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Writings, Undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Series III. Photographs, 1918-2009; 4 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 3 flat boxes, and 2 manuscript boxes
  This series consists of photographs of individuals, groups, and events Dorothy Hayden Cudahy attended, including weddings, graduations, social gatherings, musical performances, events for Irish and Irish-American organizations, award ceremonies, and dance performances by Dorothy Hayden Cudahy's Irish Steppers. The photographs date from 1918 to 2009.
  - Ancient Order of Hibernians Event, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Awards, Undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - County Clare Association Dance, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - County Clare Patriotic and Benevolent Society Association, circa 1980s (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - County Clare Patriotic and Benevolent Association--Events, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Dorothy Hayden, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 157, Folder 9)
  - Farley, Nicholas (letter on verso signed to John Hayden), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Gaelic Park, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Hanley, James "The Baron of Broadway", circa 1900s, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Hayden, James A., circa 1930s, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Hayden Cudahy, Dorothy: Social and Professional Organizations, 1918-1987; Photographs documenting Dorothy Cudahy's work at her radio program (including one photograph of James Hayden), and Dorothy and John Cudahy's involvement in social organizations. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hurling, 1929-1949 (Box Shared Tamiment 165, Folder 2)
  - Irish Institute of New York, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Irish Memories Revue, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 157, Folder 8)
  - Irish Memories Stage Revue, undated; 1950s (Box 5, Folder 3, Box 49, Folder 16, Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Irish Memories Radio Program, circa 1970s (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - The Irish Music and Social Club, 1947, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Irishwoman of the Year, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 12-13)
  - Kilkenny Association, undated (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Lovely Rose of Clare, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Martin Galvin's Return from Belfast, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Mayor's Office of New York City, 1990s (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - McAliskey, Bernadette Devlin, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Musicians, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Musicians and Performers (includes Jack Kelly, Mary O'Halloran, Tommy Hill and family, Co. Roscommon Boys Orchestra), 1900s (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - New York City Department of Traffic, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade--Grand Marshal, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 17, 21, Box 49, Folder 3)
  - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade--State Resolution, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - New York State Courts Pipes and Drums, Undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Peace Pageant: rejected Irish float, 1919? (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Politicians, circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Portrait: Bill O'Dwyer, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Portrait: Dorothy Hayden Cudahy, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Portraits (individuals) I, undated; Individual and group portraits of family and friends. Most of the photographs are unidentified. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Portraits (individuals) II, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Portraits (groups), undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Portraits: Religious ceremonies (First Communion, etc.) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Quinn, Carmel, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Rose Cottage (Rockaway), circa 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 15)